Heat. Heat.
Heat. Heat. N.
Hello everyone.
>> How are you?
>> Phenomenal. How are you?
>> Good.
>> Love to hear it.
>> Are these past uh 18 hours, what have
they been like for you? How much did you
sleep last night since you got here
today?
>> Yeah. Um, you know, they've definitely
it's gone by pretty quickly. It's it's
been a bit of a whirlwind, but in the
best way possible. You know, got up this
morning and we're close by. You know,
I'm from Cleveland originally, so we
just got up, left the house at about
10:00, got to drive up here and smooth
drive. Like, it was it was awesome. So,
it was a it was it was a fast process,
but it was smooth nonetheless. What do
you think?
>> Um, honestly, I've just been trying to
have gratitude for the moment. You know,
just enjoying the fact that, you know, I
get to drive up here and see these
amazing people, tour these amazing
facilities, you know, just the the
amount of thankfulness and gratitude
that I have in my heart right now is
incredible.
>> Excited to be back in the Midwest.
>> No, it's awesome. It definitely uh it
feels it feels good to be back here, you
know? It feels like home. So, like the
football characters kind of the driving
force in your schedule, how hard you
work, your durability, all that. What
would you say is maybe the the root of
that?
>> Um, you know, I'd really just thank my
parents for that. You know, just seeing
them my whole life, you know, they're
mortgage and real estate agents and
they're working around the clock. Didn't
matter if it was, you know, weekends,
weekdays, late at night, early in the
morning, holidays, like they were around
the clock and they were always they were
always there for their clients. and just
kind of seeing the work ethic that they
had and, you know, every every day was
working as hard as you could. And I I
kind of feel like I owe it to them to,
you know, embody that and try and go
even above and beyond.
>> Last night when we talked to Brad
Holmes, he said they have been looking
at you for like 3 years. It's one of
those situations where you never really
know like who watching like how did that
make you feel? And he's saying he he
feels like you've grown ever since they
first began looking at you just knowing
that they have been looking at you that
long and to bring you here now. No, it
definitely is really cool to hear that
they've been scouting me for that long,
but just kind of hearing his words of,
you know, how he feels I've improved
year after year. You know, obviously
every year you you shoot to improve and
to hear his confirmation on that that,
you know, he did see improvement in me
year after year and just, you know,
excited too to continue that mentality
and try and get even more and more um
technically sound and continue to
improve myself in every way possible to
be the best player I can humanly be. Do
you ever go back and and look at your
freshman year tape at Clemson just out
of curiosity and how much do you feel
like you've grown as a player since
then?
>> Yeah, I mean it'll come up every so
often. You know, we'll have a cutup or
something. Um, and it'll be on there
and, you know, it's it's crazy to see,
you know, that that four years went by
really really quickly. But just kind of
to see where I was then and where I am
now and then just the excitement for,
you know, where I'll be just this time
next year, like continuing to get
better. Like that part is super
satisfying to me, like the pursuit of
perfection.
>> He also told us a story. I I don't know
if um you know, you told him this or you
just heard it through the grape vine
that the way you started playing right
tackle was just because that was the
shortest line you got in. Can you can
you tell us that story of that?
>> Yeah. So like all throughout high school
I was a left tackle and um you know I
get to Clemson and I look and the way we
did warm-up lines obviously you know we
had left tackle, left guard, center,
right guard, right tackle and like the
warm-up line was whoever was in there
and I saw that that line was a little
shorter and just kind of by happen
stance hopped in there started repping
there and you know it God's grace it
worked out for me. You
>> just wanted to play that's all it came
down to.
>> Yeah, I just wanted to be you know
wanted to be available, wanted to get on
the field, wanted to contribute. They
always talk about kind of the
personality of offensive linemen, the
nastiness. You seem pretty soft spoken.
I'm sure all of this is quite
overwhelming, but can you kind of
describe just your mentality on the
field and and where it comes from?
>> Yeah, you know, I'd say that when I'm,
you know, just around people dayto-day,
you know, I'm a pretty even keel guy,
but when I get out on the field, you
know, I I like to bring some fire and,
you know, I try to play with a
competitive edge. You know, there's
there's nothing there's no greater
compliment as an offensive lineman than,
you know, quarter one, you know, first
play that guy's super juiced up to come
rush the passer, whatever it might be,
and then you see him end of the game and
he's looking for the sideline. Like,
that's the ultimate compliment as an
offensive lineman when you can see that.
>> You shared your first impressions on
Zoom last night about the Lions and what
you see from afar, but were you digging
up last night maybe some more? Did you
get texts from friends of, "Hey, you get
to play with this guy." What was your
overnight deep dive into the Lions if
there was one?
>> Yeah, I mean just continuing to look
more and more and I mean it just it it
made me even more excited. You know,
everything I read made me more excited.
You know, just kind of seeing some clips
of coach Campbell and, you know, I
already followed him beforehand, but
just digging even deeper now and seeing
more and more of them. Like I was ready
to run through a wall at, you know,
midnight last night, you know, just
listening to him talk. So, you know, I'm
I'm so fired up to just be a part of
this this team, this organization. What
was your read on the the Lions
throughout the process? What who did you
talk to? What were your experiences
along the way?
>> Yeah, you know, I got to I got to meet
with um them at the combine and then I
got to do like an interview via Zoom and
you know, I just with every interview
tried to put my best foot forward, learn
as much information as from the person
as I could. You know, everyone does
things a little differently and just
trying to take bits and pieces from what
everyone teaches. And you know, Coach
Freley is very intelligent. Like he was
a great teacher as well. like when he
was teaching me some of their stuff like
it was um you know it was it was easy to
learn just cuz of how great of a teacher
he is and you know him having experience
too as a player I feel like that lends
it lends itself well to him being able
to meet you where you are and help you
>> a little bit but you used to run track
you were a state champion in wrestling
I'm just curious like it's such a
diverse background for somebody of your
size and somebody of your I mean skill
set in this position how much of that
experience in your formative years
helped shaped the way you approach the
game now.
>> Yeah, I'd say the biggest one that kind
of helped shape me was wrestling. You
know, our uh wrestling coach was a
pretty nononsense guy. He was all about
toughness, all about grit. Like he'd
have us in the the wrestling room with
the the heat all the way up, you know,
95 degrees in there running around and,
you know, I'm just a little second
grader and like he he preached like
preach not quitting, like preach
toughness. And, you know, I feel like
that kind of stuck with me. You know,
you want to be a guy who's tough. You
want to be a guy who has grit. You want
to be a guy who's, you know, going to
finish and not going to crumble when
stuff gets hard.
>> Are you still in contact with that coach
at all? Is is he still in your life?
>> Uh, no, he's not. I haven't I haven't
talked to him, but
probably should.
>> When you were watching clips of Campbell
last night, were those old clips of him
or those clips of him talking about you
last night? When were those
>> No, it was like old clips of him, you
know, talking to the team, addressing
the team, talking to players, talking
about players. Just like everything he
says, you know, gets you fired up. like
he, you know, you listen to him speak
and you can hear the passion in his
voice. You can hear the care in his
voice and like that that resonates with
me and you know it it just it gets me
fired up like it gets me ready to go.
>> How about off the field? Can you give us
an idea of you know what your hobbies
are? Do you hunt, fish, skydive? What do
you what are you into besides football?
>> I'd say, you know, just just broad, you
know, being around friends, being around
family. Um, you know, I like to play
golf, like to fish,
little bit of video games, watch some TV
with the friends, you know, go out, get
some food, you know, whatever. I'm I'm
pretty easy when it comes to that stuff
as long as I'm around people who mean a
lot to me.
>> Uh, how did you feel like you stacked up
against the other tackles that were
drafted in the first round as you went
through the pre-draft process?
>> Um, you know, obviously there's a lot of
talented guys in this process and, you
know, my biggest thing was just making
sure that I was trying to be the best
version of me every day. You know, I
think, uh, comparison is the thief of
joy. So just focusing on my process day
in and day out and you know trying to be
the best I could be and you know the
guys I was training with trying to make
them better as well. Like that was my
main focus to be honest with you.
>> How comfortable were you with the idea
though that you know I guess you know
throughout your NFL career you're going
to be compared to these guys I guess and
you know ju just based on you know the
fact that you guys are all first
rounders.
>> Yeah. I mean, I'd say naturally, you
know, people are going to get compared
to one another. But at the end of the
day, it all comes back to, you know,
trying to excel in whatever role you're
in. You know, trying to be the best at
your game that you can be because, you
know, no two people are going to be the
same and everyone has different
strengths and weaknesses. But it's
trying to maximize your strengths
personally and minimize your strengths
or minimize your weaknesses, I should
say, that is really what's going to make
you the best player, at least in my
opinion. like you showed up to the
>> you're now among kind of a new group of
prospects coming through the NIL era.
What allowed you to stay committed to
Clemson and kind of just what was it
like kind of being now in in the college
game when it looks it's looking a little
more professional?
>> Yeah. Um for me like I never really
crossed my mind to transfer. Um you know
Coach Sweeney had a phenomenal program
there and you know just the the coaching
staff you had around you know coach Luke
I I had no it didn't interest me in the
slightest. You know, I felt like those
guys had been faithful and committed to
me throughout my time there, and I owed
them to do the same, and I was just I
was super happy there.
>> You uh showed up to the combine,
surprised people with your your
makeover, clean shaven in, cut hair. I'm
just curious what what went into that
decision. You think you're going to keep
the the fresh cut?
>> Um, we'll see what happens. You know,
you never know. I'll feel it out a
little bit. I'm liking it now, but we'll
see how I feel here soon. Um, but I
don't know. It just kind of happened.
You know, went wanted to get the haircut
a little shorter. It was getting in my
face and got cut a little shorter than I
thought it was going to and I was like,
"Oh, well, we're just going to roll with
this." And, you know, I'm liking it so
far, but we'll see. The the long hair
and the beard might make a return.
>> I'm just curious, uh, just Detroit in
general. It's not too far from where
you're at. Uh, what what's your
experience? Have you been to Detroit
before? What do you know about the city?
>> Uh, it's my first time here. I just know
that, you know, these fans here really
care about their sports. They're fired
up about, you know, the Lions and I I'm
just so excited to be a part of this
team and, you know, just contribute as
much as I can and really make this fan
base proud.
>> The the track, what did you participate
in? Which event?
>> I was I was shot putting discus. So, I
guess you should say, you know, field,
but we'll say track and field. Makes me
sound a little more athletic.
>> 100.
>> Um, go ahead. Uh,
>> I know it hasn't even been 24 hours yet,
but have have you talked to any of your
your new teammates yet?
>> Yeah. Um, Paneet reached out to me, Tate
reached out to me. It was kind of crazy
when um I was reading a text and at the
bottom it said Jared Golf. Like that was
a little surreal moment for me, but you
know, those guys had reached out and,
you know, just hearing from them and,
you know, seeing that they're excited,
you know, it gets me going, gets me
fired up. So, you know, I'm I'm so
excited to, you know, get here in the
building when everyone's here, meet
everyone, and get to work. I know you
said you've you've kind of watched
Paneet's game a lot. What what did it
mean to get a text from him and I guess
what did he say if you feel like Sharon?
>> Yeah. Um you know getting a text from
him was same thing. It was kind of
surreal like, you know, a guy that I'm
sitting there, you know, watching tape
on, trying to see things in his game so
I can improve things in my game and, you
know, just just getting a text from him,
you know, saying he's excited for me to
be here and excited to get to work.
Like, you know, it means a lot. And I'm
I'm just really excited to, like I said,
you know, when everyone gets here, just
really pick his brain, watch how he
works, try and, you know, glean as much
from him as I humanly can. How much do
you get the sense that uh that this
organization is similar to the Clemson
program that you you came from? I mean
just values and and the things that they
um you know uh prioritize and then also
like kind of how similar do you think
you know Dan is to to Davo?
>> Yeah. Um, you know, I'd say that there
is a lot of similarity just in terms of,
you know, they really value toughness,
they value finish, they value grit. Like
I think that was something that was
emphasized to me when I was in college
and that's something like just being
here today that I've heard a lot and it
really, you know, resonates with me and
that that's something that's near and
dear to me. So I'm, you know, that gets
me excited. Um, I just, you know, can't
say enough good things about Coach
Sweeney. Can't say enough good things
about Coach Campbell. They're two guys
who very obviously care a lot about
their players, very passionate about
what they do. You know, they get fired
up when the time calls for it. Like they
just, you know, they're two incredible
coaches.
>> What's your favorite What's your
favorite run play when it's called in
the huddle?
>> Um, probably be wide zone, you know, get
to run off the ball, get to go displace
people, and then get your back in space.
>> The uh one of the words that was used to
describe you last night a couple times
was a finisher. Um, I guess where does
that come? Like what part of your game
do you think that is? Is that work
ethic? Is that or what is it?
>> Um, I don't know if there's one specific
part. I mean, to me at the end of the
day, like it doesn't take any god-given
ability to be a guy who finishes. Like,
it's a it's a mentality. It's a mindset.
And I think that's something that was it
was stressed to me in high school. And
then coach Luke at Clemson like stressed
it a lot. Like you would, you know,
you'd get called out if you were the guy
who was letting guys come off blocks.
like it was it was expected that you're
finishing your block all the way down
the field. You shouldn't have that. You
know, some guys have the timer in their
head. Like you shouldn't have that. Like
every play has a chance to be a huge
play as long as we'll finish our block.
So that's been something that's kind of
been ingrained in me, you know, since
high school.
>> One more.
>> Like just a quick What time did you get
here today? And is that your family? Is
that what family members are here with
you?
>> Yeah, I got here at like 12:15. Um, and
then I'm here with my mom, my dad, my
girlfriend. So,
>> what position did the dad play?
>> You know, funny enough, he was uh soccer
and then he was cross country. So,
>> all right. Thank you, guys.
>> Thank you everyone.
>> How'd you get into football then?
>> He pushed me into it. Yeah,
>> I'm glad he did.
Hey,
hey, hey.
Heat. Heat.